Guide to the Eugenie V. Mielczarek papers, 1965-1997
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- American Physical Society Equal Rights Amendment Motion, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- American Institute of Physical Science Writing Prize, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- National Institute of Health Leave, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Cyclotron Resonance, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Naval Research Laboratory Proposal, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Thermal Conductivity of K (Potassium) Paper, 1967-1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Physics Department Chairman Selection, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Publication Physical Review Letters, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Abstract for APS Meeting - Some Optical Measurements of the Zaikin - Zhabotinski Reagent, 1972-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Measurements of the Ultrasonic Attenuation in Copper and Supplemental Material, July 1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Research Papers, 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Chemical Hysteresis, A New Type of Behavior in the Belousov-Zhabotinskii Reaction, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Research Contract with Atomic Energy Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Bibliography on Thermodynamics, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Schoenberg, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Correspondence from Michael Baker, August 6, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Correspondence with Ben Roberts, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Contract Report to Atomic Energy Commission, 1961-1967 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- An Experimental Study of Phase and Confirmational Notions in Lipid Structures Using Mossbauer Spectroscopy, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Luce Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Press Release, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Abstract of Paper: "Conductivity of Potassium Between 3 Kelvin and 80 Kelvin", 1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Abstract of Paper: "Catalyzed Oscillatory Reactions", 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Qu Yi, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- National Science Foundation Proposal 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- National Science Foundation Proposal 2 of 2, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- NIH Grant: "Iron Transport by Pyoverdine", 1986-1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- 3 Paper Abstracts, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Clare Boothe Luce Fund Grant 1 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Clare Boothe Luce Fund Grant 2 of 2, 1989-1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Job Letter, circa 1979 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Tracking Iron Acquisition, December 1, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- American Institute of Physics Subcommittee on Books 1 of 3, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- American Institute of Physics Subcommittee on Books 2 of 3, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- American Institute of Physics Subcommittee on Books 3 of 3, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Morgan State Seminar Nov. 16, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Marriage Tax, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Malcolm American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Kyoto, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- National Science Foundation Paper, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- National Science Foundation Paper 2, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Review Article, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Forecasts of Scientists and Engineers, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Fenwick Fellowship, 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Salary Equity Study, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 1)